<resources>
    <string name="app_name">StoryTeller</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="app_prefs">edu.tamu.storyteller</string>
    <string name="user_name">user_name_pref</string>
    <string name="user_age">user_age_pref</string>
    <string name="explanation1">Ants are very hardworking. They work in teams to bring food. Be hardworking!</string>
    <string name="explanation2">While happiness and intelligence are good, it is important to be good to others. Be peaceful!</string>
    <string name="explanation3">When someone is in trouble and they come to you, try to help!</string>
    <string name="explanation4">The dove is now in trouble. He was good and helped the ant when she needed it. Do your best to return help and favors!</string>
    <string name="explanation5">Be nice and help others. If someone helped you, return the favor!</string>
    <string name="frame1">One day, an ant was searching for some water after a long morning of work.</string>
    <string name="frame2">After walking around for some time, she came to a spring. To reach the spring, she had to climb up a blade of glass.</string>
    <string name="frame3">While making her way up, she slipped and fell into the water.</string>
    <string name="frame4">A dove was up a nearby tree enjoying the afternoon.</string>
    <string name="frame5">The dove soon saw that the ant was in trouble.</string>
    <string name="frame6">The dove quickly plucked off a leaf and dropped it into the water near the struggling ant.</string>
    <string name="frame7">The ant moved towards the leaf and climbed up there. Soon it carried her safely to dry ground.</string>
    <string name="frame8">Just at that time, a hunter nearby was throwing out his net towards the dove, hoping to trap it.</string>
    <string name="frame9">Guessing what he was about to do, the ant quickly bit him on the heel. Feeling pain, the hunter dropped his net. The dove was quick to fly away to safety.</string>
    <string name="hint1">Hint: Remember, the ant has been working all morning.</string>
    <string name="hint2">Hint: Remember, doves are always good to others.</string>
    <string name="hint3">Hint: Remember, the ant is in trouble and could drown!</string>
    <string name="hint4">Hint: Remember, the dove recently helped the ant.</string>
    <string name="hint5">Hint: Everyone needs help in some moments.</string>
    <string name="question1">What is a good quality of the ant?</string>
    <string name="option1a">Lazy</string>
    <string name="option1b">Hardworking</string>
    <string name="option1c">Thirsty</string>
    <string name="question2">What human value does the dove represent?</string>
    <string name="option2a">Peace</string>
    <string name="option2b">Happiness</string>
    <string name="option2c">Intelligence</string>
    <string name="question3">What should the dove do?</string>
    <string name="option3a">Wait, the ant will be fine.</string>
    <string name="option3b">Help the ant</string>
    <string name="option3c">Leave and go to another tree</string>
    <string name="question4">Should the ant help the dove in return?</string>
    <string name="option4a">No, it\'s the dove\'s problem.</string>
    <string name="option4b">No, wait and watch.</string>
    <string name="option4c">Yes, she should.</string>
    <string name="question5">What did you learn from the story?</string>
    <string name="option5a">Help back those who helped you.</string>
    <string name="option5b">Others never need help.</string>
    <string name="option5c">You never need help.</string>
    <string name="moral">Moral of the Story: One good turn deserves another.</string>
</resources>
